Hello
Hello everyone
In this episode
mainly want to share with you a plugin about OBACCEDING
Here's the story
This is why I really like OneNote.
Its way of opening is
where you have a notebook on the left side
Then you can see its internal situation
And here is a page
Actually, I was wondering if ABCD could achieve a similar effect.
Originally planned to use Codex to develop an OBSEIN
a plugin to achieve this specific function
but when I was chatting with ChatGPT
I suddenly came across a plugin called notebook
a plugin called Notebook Navigator
I didn't have high hopes initially
but when I went to download it
I got an interface like this
And then magically
When you open Settings in the Notebook Navigator
below in the desktop appearance
you enable the dual-pane layout
At this point, you'll discover something magical
you can quickly switch between them in ABCITY
your different notes
and it's surprisingly completely lag-free
whether it's an Excel job file or a regular Markdown file
for example here
Let's try with another file
You can see the effect is really very nice
At this point
For example, in this file there are
approximately 150 files
Each of my files has some tags
You can use these tags to control the folders
For example, under this folder
I want to go up
and then filter files with specific tags
how do I do it
I just need to hold down the control
then click here
For example, here I select content related to AI
At this point, it will filter all notes related to AI.
Of course, you can also perform multiple filters
all of this is possible
It follows exactly the same logic as OneNote.
I think it really completely solves
the issue of inconvenient file management in ABCD
and switching
You can see how fast this switching is
the switching speed between different files is very fast
At the same time, you don't have to use this folder
such a directory
You can also directly control it through tags.
For example, you can directly click on a tag you previously created
you can perform an operation
The effect is truly excellent.
I highly recommend giving it a try
Of course, here you can also choose
whether to display the contents of subfolders under your file
Currently, the subfolder contents are not displayed
Then it will be displayed
At the same time, you can also change its sorting method.
You can also change its color
including what it displays
And you can see that under each folder
It can have such an image
it follows the same logic as OneNote
is almost exactly the same
I even think it's done even better than OneNote.
Of course, you can also choose
to change its different icons
There will also be some other features
Here you can also choose to hide a folder
Then you turn off this small eye icon
Now it's not visible
Then you click on this eye icon
you can see it
You can also choose to display it here
In this way, your hidden items will appear
Then here you can click to display the calendar
You can see that it also allows you to create a list daily note
which is essentially completely replacing that Blender
the functionality of that plugin
So I highly recommend everyone to give this plugin a try
Because I haven't seen one for a long time
It's a plugin that's completely flawless in every way.
And it really doesn't lag.
file management software
I just dragged the file a little bit
it will get stuck
So everyone must give this Notebook Navigator a try.
Alright
That's all for this time
See you next time
Bye